<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>consulting on Mind the Math</title>
    <link>http://mindthemath.com/tags/consulting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in consulting on Mind the Math</description>
    <image>
      <url>http://mindthemath.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://mindthemath.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Mind the Math LLC</copyright><atom:link href="http://mindthemath.com/tags/consulting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mind the Math: Innovating at the Speed of Thought</title>
      <link>http://mindthemath.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mindthemath.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Mind the Math, where innovation meets mathematics. We are a multidisciplinary consulting firm that specializes in connecting the latest research in academia with the practical application of software development. Our goal is to help teams achieve their outcomes more effectively and efficiently by leveraging the power of technology.
Michael Pilosov, PhD Mind the Math was founded by Michael Pilosov, a computational mathematician with a unique ability to bring together scientific and creative disciplines in real-world applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service Offerings</title>
      <link>http://mindthemath.com/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mindthemath.com/services/</guid>
      <description>At Mind the Math, we offer a range of services to help teams and organizations achieve their goals more effectively and efficiently. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to improve your data science and machine learning skills, or you need help applying mathematics and software to real-world problems, we have the expertise to help.
Workshops Our workshops are designed to educate and train teams in the latest methods and techniques for data science and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
